LEO LAZZARINI

leolazz.tech | github.com/leolazz | contact@leolazz.tech

A dynamic and relentlessly driven full stack developer with a voracious appetite for skill acquisition and efficiency.

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

TYPESCRIPT | JAVASCRIPT | C# | GRAPHQL | APOLLO | ANGULAR | IONIC | REACT | NODE | DOCKER | KUBERNETES

LAZZTECH, JUNIOR FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER OCTOBER 2021 - ONGOING

Tasked with improving user experience. Contributed to front-end and back-end via ticket work including feature implementation, performance improvements, bug fixes.

- Implemented infinte scroll to notifications
- Added functionality to invite known users to a hub
- Implemented migrations and shareable-ids to entities. Inserting values into prod
 DB

ZADART EXOTIC CAR, CLIENT ADVISOR / SALES & GENERAL MANAGER APRIL 2016 – AUGUST 2020

Tasked with rental, club membership, and vehicle sales.

Prospected first leads, built relationships with high net worth individuals.

- 1# Sales 4 years in a a row out of 15+ account executives
- In first 6 months, closed 203 contracts generating 1/4 of total annual revenue
- Built long-term client relations accounting for over 30% of the yearly revenue

EDUCATION & PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SELF-DIRECTED STUDY | MENTORSHIP 2020 – ONGOING

Acheived proficiency in multiple front-end, back-end, and dev-ops tech stacks through self-directed study and one on one mentorship utilzing personal projects along with hundreds of hours of online course.

BELLEVUE COLLEGE 2014 - 2016

- Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society 4.0 GPA
- Awarded "Most Likely To Succeed" CEO Program

COMMUNITY MANAGER, STUDENTRND 2011-2013

- Represented company at University of Washington Science Expo
- Facilitated 24-hour coding competitions and mentored youths